Yeah, I-I miss you, too.
(Leonard:)Okay, sure, I'll call you
when I get home.
(Leonard:)Okay, bye-bye.
(Raj:)Very nice.
(Raj:)You lie to my sister.
(Howard:)That's the nicest thing
he does to your sister.
(cell phone ringing)
(Raj(phone rings):)Oh, guess who.
(Leonard:)Cover for me.
(Raj:)Hello, Priya. What's up?
(Raj:)How would I know
if Leonard's at work or not?
(Raj:)Don't be suspicious.
(Raj:)Look, if you want your
relationship with Leonard
(Raj:)to continue,
you're going to have to believe
(Raj:)whatever wild-eyed,
cockamamie excuse
(Raj:)the white devil
has the nerve to offer you.
(Raj:)Okay? Yeah, bye-bye.
(Raj:)You owe me.
New puzzle, Ma!
"Same name"!
One N, two D's, three O's!
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Whoopi and Rube Goldberg!
(Sheldon:)That's uncanny.
(Penny:)I know.
It's her superpower.